A Guide to the Andrew Jackson Montague Papers, 1854-1938
Library of Virginia
- X: Printed Materials, 1842-1937., Extent: 14. (Box 48-61)
  - The South and the Nation, by Andrew Jackson Montague, reprinted from The University of Chicago Magazine, volume II, number 3 (7 copies), January 1910. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - How Far the United States Supreme Court May Be Taken as a Model for an International Court of Arbitral Justice by A. J. Montague, read before the Virginia State Bar Association, (2 copies) 1910. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - List of First class Passengers [on board the] United States and Royal Mail S.S. Adriatic, from New York to Southampton,1910. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Co-operation of the States Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey Before the Governors' Conference at Frankfort, Ky.,29 November 1910. (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Democratic Campaign Book for 1910 by the National Democratic Congressional Committee, 1910. (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Dinner Tendered to Hon. John M. Harlan, Hon. Horace H. Lurton, Hon. Willis Van Devanter, and Hon. Joseph R. Lamar Justices of the United States Supreme Court by the Beta Theta Club of New York,9 February 1911. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - A Statement in Reference to teh Question of Closing the Richmond Dock,1911. (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Principles: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey before the National League of Democratic Clubs, Indianapolis, Ind.13 April 1911. (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - The Issues of Reform: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey at the Banquet of the Knife and Fork Club of Kansas City, Mo., (3 copies), 5 May 1911. (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - The Bible and Progress: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey in the Auditorium, Denver, Colo.,7 May 1911. (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Responsible Leadership: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey before the Commercial Club of Portland, Oregon,18 May 1911. (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - America as Peacemaker by S. C. Mitchell in The Religious Herald, 18 May 1911. (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Commission Government: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey at Seattle, Wash.,20 May 1911. (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Business and Politics: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey before the Publicity Club of Minneapolis, Minn., 24 May 1911. (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - The New States' Rights: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey before the Commercial Club of Lincoln, Neb.,26 May 1911. (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - A More Effective Cabinet: Address of Hon. Andrew J. Montague Delivered at the Seventeenth Annual Meeting [of the Pennsylvania Bar Association],27 June 1911. (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Democracy's Opportunity: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey at the Rally of Democratic Clubs at Harrisburg, Pa., (2 copies), 15 June 1911. (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - True Americanism, editorial reprinted from the Philadelphia North American (2 copies), 6 July 1911. (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - The Lawyer in Politics: Address of Hon. Woodrow Wilson Governor of New Jersey before the Kentucky Bar Association, Lexington, Ky., (2 copies), 12 July 1911. (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - The Hague Peace System in Operation: Cases Decided by the Permanent Court of Arbitration by James L. Tryon, reprinted from The Yale Law Journal, 1911. (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Two Notable Articles About Woodrow Wilson from the New York World and from the New York Times, 1911. (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - The Economic Utilization of History: Address by the President of the American Economic Association Henry W. Farnum at the Annual Meeting,27 December 1911. (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - General Dam Laws, Sixty-second Congress, first session, 1911. (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Seventeenth Annual Report of Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1911. (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - The Thos. S. Martin Letters, (3 copies), [1911]. (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - The People Against the Bosses: A Pamphlet of Newspaper Clippings on the Present Senatorial Campaign, Containing What William Jennings Bryan Says About Senator Thos. S. Martin, and Other Outside Views,[1911]. (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - The People Against the Bosses: Swanson's Confession Raises a Moral Issue,[1911]. (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - The Boarbour Thompson Letters Raise a Moral Issue,[1911]. (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - C. V. Meredith, The News-Leader and Alfred J. Stofer on Thos. S. Martin,[1911]. (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Senator Martin's Railroad Connections as Shown by the Barbour Thompson Letters, (2 copies), [1911]. (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Hand Book for Hon. Wiliam [sic] A. Jones and Hon. Carter Glass Addressed to the Democratic Voters in teh Primary of September 7, 1911, [1911]. (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Issued in Behalf of the Candidacy of Senator Claude A. Swanson, [1911]. (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Woodrow Wilson on Efficiency,27 January 1912. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Address of Governor Woodrow Wilson to the General Assembly of Virginia and the City Council of Richmond,1 February 1912. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Report on Alice M. Burrows and Others, Sixyt-second Congress, second session, 1912. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Speech of Hon. Albert B. Cummins, of Iowa, in the Senate of the United States, from the Congressional Record, 1912. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Public Speaking! broadside announcing A.J. Montague's appearance at Norge, Virginia, 27 July 1912. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Public Speaking! broadside announcing A. J. Montague's appearance at Toano, Virginia, 27 July 1912. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Former Governor Hon. A. J. Montague Candidate for Congress will Address the Citizens of Tabscott,9 August 1912. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - The Penrose Accusations, The Passing of Populism, and Monopoly in Moving Pictures from The Literary Digest, 31 August 1912. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Envelope, headed House of Representatives U.S., and addressed to Ex-Governor Montague,[1912]. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - The Democratic Text-Book, 1912. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Dotation Carnegie Pour La Paix Internationale: Conseil Européen title>, 1912. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Why Does Not the House Committee act upon the Pepper Bill now pending,...,[1912]. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Consumer,[1912]. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - A Budget Proposal: Speech of Hon. Swager Sherley of Kentucky in the House of Representatives,28 February 1913. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Judicial Settlement of International Disputes No. 11: Legal Problems Capable of Settlement by Arbitration by Charles Cheney Hyde, February 1913. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - River and Harbor Act,4 March 1913. (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Congressional Record, Sixty-third Congress, special session of the Senate, 5 March 1913. (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Speech of Hon. Benjamin Tillman, of South Carolina, Before the Democratic Caucus, from the Congressional Record, Sixty-third Congress, special session of the Senate, 18 March 1913. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Rescuing China from the Cross of Gold, from The Literary Messenger, volume XLVI, number 13, 29 March 1913. (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - A Bill to provide that the heads of the executive departments may occupy seats on floor of the Senate and the House of Representatives, H.R. 1938, introduced by Montague (5 copies), 7 April 1913. (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - International Neighborliness: Address of Hon. A. J. Montague, of Virginia, before the Bankers' Association of Canada and the Dominion Government, at Ottowa, Canada (4 copies), 12 June 1913. (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - The Proposed Tax on Cotton Contracts and Railroad Gross Earnings for June from The Chronicle, volume XCVII, 12 July 1913. (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - The Tariff: Speech of Hon. Ollie M. James of Kentucky in the Senate of the United States,8 September 1913. (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Bankning and Currency Bill: Speech of Hon. Robert J. Bulkley of Ohio in the House of Representatives,12 September 1913. (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - The Constitutionality of the Currency Bill: Speech of Hon. A. J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives (4 copies), 17 September 1913. (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - The Tariff Bill: Speech of Hon. A. J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives (2 copies), 30 September 1913. (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - The Fundamental Needs of Banking and Currency Reform by Murray Corrington, reprinted from the Banking Law Journal, November 1913. (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Map of Central America and the Caribbean Islands, [1913]. (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Important Roll Calls in the House of Representatives During the 63d Congress, 1st Session April 7 to December 1, 1913 compiled under the direction of Mark Sullivan, 1913. (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - The Glass-Owen Banking and Currency Law,[1913]. (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Andrew Jackson Montague in The Galaxy, [1913]. (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Hearings on the Subject of the Improvement of James River, Va. (2 copies), 16 January 1914. (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Construction and Maintenance of Rural post Roads: Supplemental Report,19 January 1914. (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - A Bill for the Relief of the Legal Representative of the Estate of Henry H. Sibley, Deceased, H.R. 12559 introduced by A. J. Montague, 28 January 1914. (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - A Bill Authorizing the Secretary of War, in His Discretion, to Deliver to the City of Richmond, Virginia, a Bronze Cannon, H. R. 12747, introduced by A. J. Montague, 31 January 1914. (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Rivers and Harbors Appropriation Bill: Report,24 February 1914. (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Panama Canal Tolls: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives (2 copies), 30 March 1914. (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - A Bill to create an Interstate Trade Commission, to define its powers and duties, and for other purposes, H.R. [no number], committee print, March 1914. (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - A Bill to amend..."an Act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters..., S. [no number], committee print--confidential, March 1914. (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - A Bill for the relief of the legal representatives of the estate of Henry H. Sibley, deceased, H.R. [no number]. 1914. Bill contains Montague's handwritten changes to Senate bill 1851. (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Interstate Trade Commission: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague, of Virginia, in the House of Representatives,21 May 1914. (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Banking and Currency Act: Speech of Hon. John F. Shafroth of Colorado in the Senate of the United States,27 May 1914. (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - A Bill to facilitate the use of square numbered six hundred and seventy-three, in the city of Washington, for storage warehouse purposes, H.R. 16904, introduced by A. J. Montague (2 copies), 28 May 1914. (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - A bill to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters..., H.R. 16053, Union Calendar No. 270, 1914. (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - A bill for the relief of W. T. Brogdon, H.R. 17594, introduced by A. J. Montague, 30 June 1914. (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Labor Legislation: Address of Hon. David J. Lewis of Maryland in the House of Representatives,3 September 1914. (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - On Mount Ararat: Address of John Skelton Williams, in Indianapolis, Indiana, 29 September 1914. (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Daily Statement of the United States Treasury at the close of business,21 October 1914. (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Address Delivered by Miss Mildred Lewis Rutherford Historian General United Daughters of the Confederacy: Wrongs of History Righted,13 November 1914. (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Importan Roll-Calls in the United States Senate, Sixty-Third Congress, First Session,1914. (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - The Interparliamentary Union: Handbook of the American Group, 1914. (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Achievements of Eighteen Months of Democracy, Let the Republican Party Answer These Questions, Voters of Maine, Accomplishments of Woodrow Wilson's Administration, How Congress Has Voted, and Think This Over, Mr. Voter, campaign cards, 1914. (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Proceedings of the Virginia Historical Society at Its Annual Meeting Held in the House of the Society, 1915. (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - The Horse in all Civilizations: Speech of Hon. Isaac R. Sherwood, of Ohio, in the House of Representatives,4 March 1915. (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - An Act Making appropriations for the construction, repair, and preservation of certain public works on rivers and horbors, and for other purposes, H.R. 20189, [4 March 1915]. (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - International Law as Applied by England During the War: II. Trading with the Enemy by Norman Bentwich, reprinted from The American Journal of International Law, April 1915. (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - A Secretary of State from Brown, William Learned March--an Address by John Bassett Moore, adn Brotherhood--a Poem by Henry Robinson Palmer, 15 June 1915. (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - The Monroe Doctrine, address by A. J. Montague to the State Bar Association of Indiana (2 copies), July 1915. (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Henry Clay and Pan-Americanism by John Bassett Moore, reprinted from The Columbia University Quarterly, September 1915. (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - Report of the Chief Engineer of the U.S. Army on river and harbor improvements in Virginia, 1915. (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - A Bill to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, S. 3331, Sixty-fourth Congress, first session, 10 January 1916. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Hearings on the Subject of the Improvement of James River, Va. held before the Committee on Rivers and Harbors House of Representatives Sixty-fourth Congress,18 January 1916. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - River and Harbor Appropriation Bill: views of a Minority,23 February 1916. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - A bill to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, S. 3331, Sixty-fourth Congress, first session, March 1916. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - An act to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, S. 3331, Union calendar 121, Sixty-fourth Congress, first session, March 1916. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - An act to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, etc., as passed by the Senate, and the House substitute therefor, Sixty-fourth Congress, first session, 1916. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - A bill to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, H.R. 16053, committee print with amendments, March 1916. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - James River, Va.: Letter from the Secretary of War, House of Representatives, Sixty-fourth Congress, first session, May 1916. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - The Fortification Appropriation Bill: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives (2 copies), 12 June 1916. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Investigation Showing the Effect of Price Cutting on Trade-Marked Grocery Articles in Greater New York by Raymond B. Callahan, [June 1916]. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - An act making appropriations for the construction, repair, and preservation of certain public works on rivers and harbors, and for other purposes, H.R. 12193, Public--no. 168, Sixty-fourth Congress, 1916. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - We Challenge all Comers: Achievement vs. Evasion by Woodrow Wilson, 30 September 1916. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Bond Issue: Report, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session (2 copies), 11 April 1917. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - A bill to authorize an issue of bonds to meet expenditures for the national security and defense, and to extend credit to foreign governments, and for other purposes, H.R. 2762, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session, 11 April 1917. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - A bill to authorize an issue of bonds to meet expenditures for the national security and defense, and to extend credit to foreign governments, and for other purposes, H.R. [no number], confidential, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session, 11 April 1917. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Bond Issue: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague of Virginia in teh House of Representatives,14 April 1917. (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Give $1,000,000,000 to France A Debt of Duty and Gratitude: Editorials from the New York World, 1917. (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - A bill to define, regulate, and punish trading with the enemy, and for other purposes, committee substitute for H.R. 4960, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session, June 1917. (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - A bill to define, regulate, and punish trading with the enemy, and for other purposes, H.R. [no number], committee print, 28 June 1917. (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Executive Order of President Woodrow Wilson, 30 June 1917. (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - A Bill in relation to trading with the enemny, H.R. 5325, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session, (edits in pencil), 6 July 1917. (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - A gill to amend and act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, S. 1419, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session, 12 July 1917. (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Constitutional Amendment with Relation to National Prohibition by James T. Lloyd, 30 July 1917. (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - A bill to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, H.R. [no number], committee print, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session (3 copies), July 1917. (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - An act to give effect to the convention between the United States and Great Britain for the protection of migratory birds concluded at Washington, August sixteenth, nineteen hundred and sixteen, and for other purposes, S. 1553, in House of Representatives, Sixty-fifth Congress, first session, 3 August 1917. (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - A bill to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, H.R. 7695, Sixty-fifth Congress, second session (3 copies), 14 December 1917. (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - An act to amend an act to regulate the construction of dams across navigable waters, S. 1419, in the House of Representatives, Sixty-fifth Congress, second session (2 copies), 15 December 1917. (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - By the President of the United States of America, A Proclamation: Possession and Control of Rail and Water Transportation Systems,26 December 1917. (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - A bill granting an increase of pension to Janet K. Glennnon, H.R. 8959, introduced by A. J. Montague, Sixty-fifth Congress, second session, 18 January 1918. (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - A bill to provide for the operation of transportation systems while under federal control, for the just compensation of their owners, and for other purposes, H.R. 9685, committee print, Sixty-fifth Congress, second session, 8 February 1918. (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - An act to provide for the operation of transportation systems while under Federal control, for the just compensation of their owners, and for other purposes, S. 3752, Sixty-fifth Congress, second session, [21 February 1918]. (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Joint resolution proposing an amendment to the Constitution of the United States regarding the right to vote, H.J. Res. 283, Sixty-fifth Congress, second session (2 copies), 29 April 1918. (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - The Aviator's Hymn by Sally Nelson Robins, 3 June 1918. (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - They Call Them Devil-Hounds but They Are Simply Hounding the Devil--Our Marines, broadside, 20 June 1918. (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - International Conciliation: The League of Nations, number 131, October 1918. (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Pertinent Paragraphs about the Transportation Corps: What It Was and What It Did in the A.E.F.,[1918]. (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Amendment to sections 1, 2, and 3, H.R. 8172, which gives the president authority to take over the transporation system, [1918]. (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Postcard of the tomb of Lieutenant Quentin Roosevelt in France. Card is written in French, [1918]. (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - The President and the Peace Conference: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives (2 copies), 14 January 1919. (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - The President and the Peace Conference: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives, galley proofs, [1919]. (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Chesterfield County in War Time: A Community History by Laura Martin Wheelwright (2 copies), [1919]. (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Nerve Force by Paul von Boeckmann, 1919. (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Theodore Roosevelt: A Biographical Sketch and Excerpts from His Writings and Addresses by Hermann Hagedorn, 1919. (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Weight-Control for Health, Beauty, and Efficiency by Eugene Christian for the Corrective Eating Society, twelve booklets, 1919. (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Memorial Addresses on the Life and Character of William A. Jones, 1919. (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Spanish Policy toward Virginia, 1606-1612; Jamestown, Ecija, and John Clark of the Mayflower by Irene A. Wright, reprinted from American Historical Review, volume XXV, number 3, April 1920. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Elks' Home Bulletin, Richmond Lodge, no. 45, B.P.O.E.,[August 1920]. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Truths of History by Mildred Lewis Rutherford, [1920?]. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague, of Virginia, in the House of Representatives, printed in the Congressional Record, 18 January 1921. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - River and Harbor Improvements: Letter from teh Secretary of War, Sixty-seventh Congress, first session, May 1921. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Water Terminal and Transfer Facilities: Letter from the Secretary of War, Sixty-seventh Congress, first session, July 1921. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - A bill granting the consent of Congress to the Pamunkey Ferry Company to construct a bridge across the Pamunkey River in Virginia, H.R. 9050, introduced by A. J. Montague, Sixty-seventh Congress, first session (9 copies), 9 November 1921. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - A bill authorizing appropriations and contracts for the prosecution and maintenance of public works on canals, rivers, adn harbors, and for other purposes, S. 2881, Sixty-seventh Congress, second session (3 copies), 19 December 1921. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - River and Harbor Bill: Report, Sixty-seventh Congress, second session, 7 March 1922. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Arthur Burt shoe company advertisements, 1922. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Twentieth Conference of the Interparliamentary Union, Vienna, Austria, August, 1922 by Arthur Deerin Call, reprinted from Advocate of Peace (2 copies), September 1922. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - George Washington: Address of Hon. A. J. Montague, of Virginia, before the University of Pennsylvania (2 copies), 22 February 1923. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Child-Labor Amendment to the Constitution of the United States: Report, Sixty-eighth Congress, first session (2 copies), 28 March 1924. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - A bill for the relief of Claude S. Betts, late ensign (pilot) Naval Air Service, H.R. 8566, introduced by A. J. Montague, Sixty-eighth Congress, first session, 9 April 1924. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Child-Labor Constitutional Amendment: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives (2 copies), 26 April 1924. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - The Relation of Government to Private Business Enterprise by Nicholas Murray Butler, 15 May 1924. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - A Short Account of the Temple Church [in Jerusalem], 1924. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - The New Republic, volume XL, number 514, 8 October 1924. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - The New Republic, volume XL, number 517, 29 October 1924. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Reflections on Armistice Day: Address of Mr. Samuel Untermyer,11 November 1924. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Proposed Child Labor Amendments to the Constitution of the United States: Hearings before the Committee on the Judiciary, House of Representatives, Sixty-eighth Congress, second session (2 copies), 1924. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Business card for Weldon and Sons, jewellers and silversmiths, Dublin, Ireland, [1924?]. (Box 55, Folder 22)